It's been a long time.
お久しぶりです
Is this enough for each time?
一回ずつこれくらいかな?
Well, that's about it.
そうですね、それくらいですね
Hey, you're cute again.
ねえ、可愛くなったな、また
You got your hair cut.
髪切りましたね
I got my hair cut.
髪切りました
It looks great on you.
すごい似合っちゃいます
How have you been?
元気だったの?
Well, I've been busy lately, but...
そうですね、最近いろいろ忙しいんですけど、
I'm doing well.
元気にしてます
I'm busy, lots of things.
忙しいんだ、いろいろ
yes.
はい
Is it work?
仕事ですか?
I'm working hard and it's been a little busy.
頑張ってて、それがちょっと忙しいです
You're not an idol now, right?
今はアイドルやってないんだよね?
Yes, I'm not an idol.
はい、アイドルはやってないんですけど
What?
何を?
Which way?
どの方で?
I'm aiming to become an actress.
女優目指してて
It was on sale.
売ってたね
Yes, that's right.
はい、そうです
So, did anything come out?
で、何か出た?
I have a lot of money now, and I'm going through a lot of auditions and things like that.
今、量入ってるんですけど、それでいろいろオーディションとか受
I also work as an extra at work.
け たり、仕事としてはエキストラとかやってたりしてます
That's right.
そうなんだ
The amount is huge.
量、大変だね
Like girl power?
女子力みたいな?
that's right.
そうです
An office?
事務所が?
There are children who are aiming for various things.
いろいろ目指してる子がいるんで
That's right.
そうなんだ
That looks amazing, over there.
すごいそうだね、あそこ
Can I go too?
俺も行っていいのかな?
You're not trying hard right now.
頑張ってないでしょ、今ね
I want to support you.
応援したいです
A while ago, I'm sorry, something happened.
ちょっと前はね、ごめんね、何か
It's a bit forced.
なんか、ちょっと無理やりに
I've put the deleted version here,
その消してもらったのをここにしたんで、
I'll come too.
私も来ると
Since then, we've been in contact for a little longer,
あれからさ、もうちょっと連絡も長くなったから、
I thought you were a little more angry,
もうちょっと怒っちゃったなって思ったんだけど、
But I'm glad you're here again.
でもまた来て、嬉しいですよ、来てくれて
Why did you come here again?
なんでまたこれ、来てくれた?
Even though I go to various auditions,
いろいろオーディションとか受けるのに、
I see.
なるほどね
That's a little bit on the edge.
それがもうちょっとギリギリで
Does it cost a lot after all?
やっぱりいろいろかかる?
It will take.
かかります
It's all at my own expense.
全部自費なんで
自費?
Mostly, yes.
ほとんど、そうですね
What do you mean by costumes?
衣装とか、どういうこと?
I had to practice various dances and things.
いろいろダンスとかも練習したりしなきゃいけなくて、
Lesson tables and costumes like that cost a lot of money.
そういうレッスン台とか、衣装とかも結構かかっちゃうんですね
I can get some out of it.
多少出してもらえるんですけど
Do I have to bear the burden too?
自分も負担じゃいけないの?
That's tough, isn't it?
大変だね、それは
I feel like this is just what I need.
これでちょっと必要だね、みたいな
I absolutely support that.
全然全然全然それは支援しますけど
That's like a papakatsu, like a dating cloud,
あれはパパカツみたいな、交際クラウドみたいな、
Are you still doing that?
あれはまだやってるんですか?
If I found out I was an actress, I would be a little scared of the company, etc.
女優バレたらちょっと会社とかに怖くて、
Not so much now, yeah.
あんまり今、 そうですね
Don't you do much?
あんまりやってない?
I don't really know what to do.
あんまりどうしようかなって
Did you meet anyone after that?
あの後に誰かと会ったりした?
I see you.
会ってますね
But I feel like I'm a little short on money.
でもなかなかちょっとお金も寂しいって
I agree.
そうですね
That's because I want to support dreams.
それは夢を応援したいって
Let's do our best.
頑張りましょう
I will do my best.
頑張ります
Let's do our best. I have to try my best.
頑張りましょうっていうか、俺は頑張んじゃいけないんですよ
how was it?
どうだった?
A while before I was photographed.
撮られてみて、その前ね、ちょっと
I took some more cuts.
またカットとか撮っちゃった
I really didn't like it.
やっぱちょっと嫌だった
It was embarrassing.
恥ずかしかったですね
Yeah.
うん
That's right.
そうだよね
I'll take a picture today.
今日撮っちゃうよ
Is it still today?
今日もですか?
Today too.
今日も
I'll take pictures today too.
撮 っちゃうよ、今日も
Well, it's fun.
まあまあ、楽しくね
If only I could do it.
やれたら
If you can erase it in the end...
最後消してもらえるなら...
Have fun.
楽しくね
So cute.
可愛いな
It's cute, as always.
可愛いっすね、相変わらずね
That hairstyle suits you.
似合ってますよ、その髪型
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Like this, idol...
こんなさ、アイドル...
Although it's an ex.
元だけど
I can't touch my head, that's normal.
頭触れないよね、普通
hey.
ね
Usually.
普通は
I'm so curvy.
プリプリしてる
Pre-puri.
プリプリ
I won't force myself like that today.
今日はそんな無理やりやんないからね
If you don't like it, it's okay if you don't like it.
嫌だったら、さあ、嫌だっていいから
But you like edges, right?
でも、エッジ好きでしょ?
I thought.
思った
You really like it, right?
本当は好きでしょ?
I was out for a while.
ちょっと出てたもん
You're really good at blowjobs.
フ ェ ラットがすごい上手いよね
Who taught you this?
誰に教わったの?
I guess I was a weak member, really.
弱い会員したのね、本当
A taught me something today.
今日はAの教わったもんね
difficult?
難しい?
These legs are beautiful.
ここ足、綺麗だね
Special.
スペシャル
I pay a lot of attention to my beauty.
結構美容には気を遣ってしてる
Are you doing it?
してる?
Are you saying Leste?
レステとか言ってる?
Actresses have to work hard.
女優、頑張らなきゃいけないんで
That's right.
そうだよね
A beautiful person.
綺麗な人
That's amazing, Tune.
すごいね、チューン
You're good at it.
上手いね
After all, in lessons, we study things like kissing scenes.
やっぱ、レッスンでさ、キスシーンとか勉強するの
It's so cute.
すごい可愛いよね
That's a cute tune.
可愛いチューンだね
I guess I'll show you a little bit today.
今日はちょっと見せてくれるんだね
Look behind you?
後ろ見てごらん?
Look this way?
こっち向いてごらん?
Smooth.
さらさら
Like water.
水みたいな
Pussy, would you please open it?
マンコさん、開いてごらん?
By yourself.
自分で
Beautiful pussy.
綺麗なマンコ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?